if yours surrendered and then tried
если бы ваши сдались а потом судили бы
those who occupied you, you wouldn’t
тех которые вас оккупировали не было бы
really understand that the Ukrainians soaked the
реально понимаешь что украинцы мочили
Ukrainians pumped Ukraine very strongly
украинцы украину очень сильно накачивают
with weapons and well we can defend ourselves, we defend ourselves
оружием и хорошо мы можем мы защищаемся
a lot of peaceful ones, while
защищаемся очень много мирных при этом
wherever you
где бы
look, I’ll ask people with Russia
смотрите я вот людей с россией
how you feel  you don’t know about the war
спрашивать как вы относитесь к войне
boucle,
букле не
I’m not afraid and I myself am from Bavaria, you
знаете я не страхи и сам из баварии мне
just show yourself to me in communication in Russia
просто показываете себя в общении россии
yes, unfortunately I don’t know how to
да я к сожалению не знаю как мне
change the settings to show
изменить настройки чтобы показывать и
you yourself from where the flu is true when drunk I
так сами откуда гриппе верным в пьяном
don’t use
не пользуюсь
yes but if I’m so small you yes
да но если я такой небольшой вас да
then  negative attitude before the war,
тогда негативное отношение до войны
but towards the war, and you know, there is no such
но к войне и ты знаешь нет такого
one-sided attitude; my guys
однобокого отношения у меня ребята
are resting Russians; I am the owner of the hotel;
отдыхают русские я владелец отеля
Russian speaking German;
русский говорящий с германией они
so
для может обидно что-то скажу вот так
I call the saucepan because they make a
называю кастрюльке потому что они шумят
lot of noise they swear they swear in Russian,
много ругаются ругаются на русский язык
and on those who  Germans
причем на тех которые этим русским
have been using the Russian language for the last 30 years
языком пользуются последние 30 лет
why they do this, I don’t understand either,
германии почему они так делать я тоже не
I understand that he is somewhere with
понимаю я понимаю что он где-то
upset feelings and, well, somehow emotions,
расстроенных чувствах и ну как-то эмоции
I guess I probably
наверно я наверно прибалтийский
need to hide the emotions of the Baltic mentality deeper,
менталитета надо эмоции прятать поглубже
but for me it’s unacceptable that people
но для меня это неприемлемо что люди
are fighting with monuments to women  who
воюют с памятниками женщинами которые
speak Russian there was one individual
по-русски говорят был один индивидуум
not far from the city he fought with products
недалеко городе он воевал с продуктами
that are Russian
которые российские
which is why I think that this is correct and
чего почему я считаю что это правильно и
that is, economic sanctions here he makes a contribution at
то есть экономические санкции вот он на
his level
своем уровне
absolutely we carry out look
абсолютно проводим смотри
they damaged a car that has a
они повредили машину у которой есть
Russian flag for
российский флаг
example on the windshield
допустим на лобовом стекле
moreover, a person who has a
причем человек который у которого
Russian fact on the glass, he didn’t get
российских факт на стекле он не полез
any losses,
никаких убытков
suffered losses, an insurance company
понесла убытки страховая компания
which in Germany has
которая в германии
to do with it in general, this is the relationship,
при чем тут вообще вот это вот отношения
let’s
допустим тот же памятник
take a good look at the same monument, let’s do it, and if a
рассмотрите хорошо давайте так а если
person hangs himself a fascist
человек повесить себе фашистскую
swastika like that on the windshield,
свастику так на лобовое стекло
this is normal
это нормально
no no
нет нет а
but with such a statement  you want to show
вот таким утверждением хочешь показать
that you equate the Russian flag yes yes the
что российский флаг приравниваешь да да
point is where in the fact that now such
дело где в том что сейчас такие
people are perceived before Russia there is
воспринимается до россии есть
a fascist state
государство фашист я по жизни и борьбы
I don’t know why how
войны как таковой нету знать почему как
not why ukraine why how to Odessa
нет почему украина почему как одессит
go to russian from latvia you are not a
идите ка я в русский из латвии вы не
russian Latvian  or a
русский или латыш
socially official Latvian Ukraine did not
социально официального украина не
enter the war to know why he will tell
вступило войну знать почему он расскажет
and the husband or the country will enter the war she
а муж или страна вступит войну она не
will not be able to receive help and now look
сможет получать помощь а теперь смотрите
I will tell them the
я им скажу
war is not necessarily announced so
война не обязательно оглашается так
now there is a war going on in Ukraine
сейчас в украине проходит война
let's do it and Hitler when he attacked the
давайте так а гитлер когда напал на
Soviet Union he announced  war
советский союз он огласил войну
for 3, that is, there was no war for three days,
на 3 то есть три дня не была война
that is, war, look, yes, war can
то есть война смотрите да война может
be without declaring war, true,
быть без объявления войны правда
yes, that is, declaring war is just
да то есть объявление войны это просто
a kind of legal fact, so that it does not
некий юридический факт так который не
cancel and not
отменяет и не
that war is true, that is,
что что война есть правда то есть
for example,
например
military actions they can  to be without
военные действия они могут быть без
declaring war there are 2 sexes, that is,
объявления войны тут 2 полов то есть
war is
война
simply because there is such a
просто тому что есть вот такой
legal one as you  you steal a cap if
юридический как ты говоришь картуз если
war is declared, those who help
будет объявлена война те кто помогает
ukraine ukraine automatically become
украине украине автоматически становятся
enemies of russia look yes but war is
врагами россии смотрите да но война
theirs but war is going on this war is going on this war
своей но война идет война идет эта война
which without declaring war
которая без объявления войны
see for example here we took and
смотрите например вот мы с вами взяли и
fought without declaring a fight there is
побились без объявления драки вот есть
a duel let's go out on
на дуэль давайте выйдем по бьемся это
we fight, so we went to a duel, but we walked and walked, I took it and attacked you for some reason, and here we are fighting, this is a fight, there was no
вот мы бьемся это драка никакого
declaration of a fight, it’s true,
объявления драки не было правда
that is, it’s the same with war if we
то есть так так же и с войной если мы
look at international documents like this  and
посмотрим международные документы так и
the same Geneva convention of Tomsk, even
женевскую ту же конвенцию томская даже
if the war squats without and about the
если война приседать без и об
announcement, and
объявлении и
now you have some kind of such a position about a
вот у вас какая-то такая позиция про
fascist, you now somehow
фашистка вы сейчас как-то вот это
whiten them for the Russian occupiers and
оккупантам российских вы их отбеливает и
I'm not saying that they are white fluffy yes I
я не говорю что они белые пушистые да у
have here  the guys who
меня тут есть ребята которые spot
got out of the spot waves, I
волновахи выбрались я им реально
really help them financially, they are in
материальном помогаю они находятся в
Murnau near my Bavarian region in the
мурнау рядом с моим баварским регионом в
clinic, they even save their legs there, that is,
клинике им там даже ноги спасают то есть
we are there  we write to the Spasskaya, everything
мы там переписываемся спасской все
else, yes, he sent Easter cake there so that
остальное да посылал туда кулич вот чтоб
everything was I’m not against the Ukrainians,
все было я не против украинцы как как
just that they just get it, so I’m not against
раз они просто получать вот я не против
100, I’m not against the Russians who, let’s say,
100 я не против россиян которые допустим
came to Germany,
приехали в германию
but when your people come here, they don’t
но ваши люди когда приезжают сюда не не
share anything at all, they didn’t know how
делят вообще ничего не умели ни еще
someone else who understands with rabid and now yours
кого-то понимающие с оголтелые и вот ваш
turns into rabid rabid
превращается в оголтелых оголтелыми быть
you can’t be in Europe, but look, it’s
нельзя в европе а вот смотрите
not the moment, I’ll just say that how it
не момент я просто скажу что чем это
ends, they will set their gold
закончится они своей gold целости
integrity on the rest of the German people,
настроят на весь остальной народ
not the government, the people against the
немецкий не правительство народ против
Ukrainians and no one else will help
украинцев и никто больше помогать не
it will be, but it’s good, but tell me
будет а вот хорошо а вот скажите вот
now in Germany now the Germans
сейчас в германии сейчас немцы
are responsible to those killed
несут ответственность перед убитыми
when you are Jews
когда ты евреями
but morally a mistress yes yes
но морально любовницу да да да
yes look like this, these are Germans who were already
вот так смотрите это немцы которые уже
born even here were born far after the
родились даже тут родились далеко после
war for some reason they are
войны почему-то они несут
responsible for the atrocities of the Germans
ответственность за злодеяния немцев
who  were then in the Third Reich
которые были тогда в третьем рейхе
absolutely the same these Russians they
абсолютно the same вот эти русские они
bear moral responsibility  for the
несут моральную ответственность за
actions of their country, citizens who
действия их страны гражданами которые
they are
они есть
citizens of latvia and lithuania and estonia in the worlds of the country of
граждане латвии и литвы и эстонии мирах
uzbekistan, they definitely
стана узбекистана они определенно
become russian-speaking germany they are
становится русскоговорящими германии их
not divided at all so that you understand
не делят вообще никак чтоб ты понимал
they came from the soviet union spoke
они приехали советского союза говорили
in russian they became russian-speaking
на русском языке они стали
it does not mean that he is a
русскоговорящими это не значит что он
russian they support there
россиянин там поддерживают там кого-то
Lisa is some kind of political scare, even
какой-то политические струшу лизе я даже
when I live in Germany, I don’t always understand what’s
живя в германии я не всегда понимаю что
going on with me, and because I don’t have
происходит у меня влад и потому что у
my own worries, I’m not interested in TV
меня свои заботы не интересен телевизор
at all, like I don’t even watch youtube,
вообще не как я даже youtube практически
because all the time at work
не смотрю потому что все время на работе
you understand  I hear echoes
понимаешь до меня доносится отголоски
here are the guys who come and
вот ребята который приезжают
tell me how in the fifteenth year
рассказывают как в пятнадцатом году ко
guys from the Donbass came to me who
мне приезжали ребята с донбасса который
ran away from there, but they also do
убежали оттуда но они тоже ничего лицо
n’t tell me anything pleasant about your face,
приятного про ваших не рассказываю
believe me to wear they fled to
поверь мне носить они они убежали в
Europe they are in Russia and why but
европу они в россии а почему но потому
because he had
что у него был
option to go outside of school, he began
вариант пойти не по учёбе он начинал
to study in the fourteenth year of his
учиться в четырнадцатом году его
birth  whether they just stayed just
родители остались просто просто на
look at like the storm began, the storm began, he
смотрите-ка like буча началась буча он
managed to transfer his parents, the
успел своих родителей перевестись просто
Russians just tell us that they
нам русские говорят что они вот этот
came to the Donbass because
зашли в донбасс так потому что
Ukraine wanted to go to Europe and the Donbass did not
украина хотела в европу а донбасс не
want to go to Europe, and then it turns out that he, on the
хотел в европу и тут получается что он
contrary, runs away from the Donbass  I see this
наоборот из донбасса убегает вижу этот
conflict, I don’t bring it out, not like me, even from
конфликт не вывожу не как я даже вот со
all sides, I don’t understand it, I
всех сторон я его ну не понимаю я
really understand that the Ukrainians soaked the
реально понимаю что украинцы мочили
Ukrainians, all this is an opinion of the salts
украинцев все вот это мнение солей там
from which the Donbas conflict began on April 12
из чего начался конфликт донбассе 12
, 14, so a group of Russian
апреля 14 года так группа русских
saboteurs entered from Russia captured the
диверсантов зашла из россии захватила
city of Slavyansk
город славянск
from this it began
вот с этого и начался
before the Russian troops arrived
до того как туда пришли русские войска
there, in general, everything was calm, the rallies
там вообще все было спокойно митинги
were normal, that is, ordinary Ukrainian
были обычной то есть обычных украинской
internal political life, everything after that
внутриполитической жизнь все после этого
they captured, the instructor’s weapons began to be transferred through Russia,
они захватили началась через россию
and so
перебрасываться оружие инструктора и так
on, everything is
дальше все
okay, well, thanks,
окей хорошо спасибо
just one of the ovens that Ukraine  very
просто одни из печи что украину очень
heavily pumped with weapons and well we
сильно накачивают оружием и хорошо мы
can we defend ourselves defend ourselves a
можем мы защищаемся защищаемся очень
lot of m  At the same time, the innocents are dying, wait, but
много мирных при этом гибнут подождите а
it doesn’t seem to you that they are dying because
вам не кажется что гибнут из-за того что
we have nothing to defend ourselves,
у нас не чем защищаться а
but one question is if yours surrendered and
вот один вопрос если бы ваши сдались а
then they would judge those who occupied you,
потом судили бы тех которые вас
see if, for example, someone comes
той смотрите если например кто-то придет
to rape you, it’s better that
вас изнасиловать то лучше что вы сдались
you surrendered, raped you, and then you sued,
у вас изнасиловали а потом вы судились
or is it better to defend yourself a little
или все-таки лучше защищаться немного
differently, for
другое почему
some reason I forgot about creating no matter how no one there,
то забыла про создать как никто бы там
no matter how atrocities, nothing and ports, this is to
ни зверства ничего и порты это вот
judge and sanctions
судить и санкции
Volodya, that is, we had to surrender
володе то есть мы мы должны были сдаться
so that we were cut out here like that
чтобы нас тут вырезали так и бы
after all, under occupation, that is, you are now
ведь под оккупацией то есть вы вы сейчас
you
вы
save lives, this is a priority for you, I
сохранить жизни это приоритет вам про я
understand correctly that when Nazi
правильно понимаю что когда гитлеровская
Germany attacked other countries, according to
германия нападала на другие страны по
your logic, and countries had
вашей логике и странам надо было
to surrender in order to save lives, so in
сдаваться чтоб сохранить жизни так во
France very few people died, what
франции очень мало человек погибло как
do you think, why because  that they
ты думаешь почему потому что очень
broke all the resistance very quickly
поломали все сопротивление очень быстро
captured France the resistance of the
захватили франции сопротивление
resistance side by side with him in general
сопротивления о бок с ним вообще вот
France surrendered in three days so yes  she
франция сдалась за три дня так да она
surrendered and the civilian population died there
сдалась и там погибло мирного населения
very much,
очень а
and the Jews they fought against for they didn’t
и евреи они воевали против для не
give up, so the Jews didn’t have any
сдались вот евреи никакого сопротивления
resistance to the phenomenon, unfortunately at that time the
не явлению к сожалению на тот момент у
Jews didn’t have it so look, the Jews generally
евреев не было так смотри евреи вообще
didn’t resist they were
получается не сопротивлялись на их
destroyed by millions both in Germany
уничтожали миллионами так в германию так
and in the occupied  territories,
и на оккупированных территориях
this is how it turns out and you are telling us here that
так получается и вы тут нам говорите что
if you surrendered, it would be
давайте если вы сдались вам было бы
better for you,
лучше
I think that life is priceless if you
я считаю что жизнь она бесценна если и
don’t save it, then all these flutterings,
не сохранить то вот эти все трепыхания
well, you don’t understand that if you are
ну вы не понимаете что если вас
captured, then even more life will go away
захватывают то еще больше жизни уйдет
tried here we tried tried
пробовали вот мы пробовали пробовали
look so that we are part of the
смотрите чтоб мы были в составе
Soviet Union, we remember what the
советского союза мы помним что такое
Holodomor is, we remember the twenties, we
голодомор мы помним двадцатые годы мы
remember 30, and so on, how much Russia
помним 30 и так дальше сколько россия
killed at the brink and Ukrainians by the millions
убивала у грань и украинцы миллионами
Unfortunately, I can’t answer you
сожалению не могу тебе ответить по
about the Holodomor, but there are a lot of
поводу голодомора да там очень куча
different sources, and someone says that
разных источников да кто то говорит что
it was a mistake, the management, someone
это была ошибка руководство кто то
says that this was
говорит что это спланированная акция
some kind of planned action, it was worth a million  a million dead
какая-то была на миллион миллион убитых
yes I can’t truthfulness image conclusion
да не могу правдивость изображение вывод
right you have some kind of
прям у вас какая то знаете
syndrome such an excuse for the aggressor
синдром такой оправдание агрессора
there is there I say there is because it
есть есть вот я говорю есть потому что
looks better for you to give up, that is,
выглядит вам лучше было сдаться то есть
for example, you know it’s like a brand situation
например знаете это как ситуации марки
what motive is that people live in their mind
какой мотив такое что люди жить они уме
on March 1, see  it means that when
1 марта смотрите значит это когда снова
we take the bandit again, he wants to rape the
возьмем бандит хочет изнасиловать
girl and he beat her because she
девушку и он ее побил потому что она
resisted and choose, and if she didn’t
сопротивлялась и выберите а если она не
resist, then he would just
сопротивлялась то он бы просто
rape him and then sue sanctions,
изнасиловал и дальше засудили санкции
but you see, it’s not clear
вводили но видишь непонятно какой
some kind of European approach, I’m just a
какой-то европейский подход я просто
human life is priceless and when  and they
человеческая жизнь бесценна а когда и
start stuffing you with weapons and
вас начинают пичкаете оружием и
killing you, I’m not talking about the military, I’m talking
убивают я не говорю про военных я говорю
about the civilian population that
про мирное население что его становится
there are many times more of the dead, but it’s not
в разы больше мертвых это но это
normal, is it then that you
ненормально то ли вы тогда тогда
somehow endure military operations outside the
выносить как-то военные действия за
cities so that the answer is that
города чтобы ответ
civilians die because  that we are
мирные у погибают из-за того что мы
defending ourselves or because the aggressor
защищаемся или из-за того что агрессор
attacked the aggressor on the floor, it’s anyway, yes,
напал агрессор на полу это по-любому да
I’m not talking about that
я тебе не об этом все налоги от себя
all the taxes from myself said that when, let’s say, yours put hailstones, well, the video already exists, yes, there are colors, views that don’t live, the building rejected it, it arrives lived and look, Mariupol, they didn’t see in the news what Mariupol is so bombed with air bombs, they gave such grades there, then they just level it with the ground, the Russians just level it with the ground, so someone is there and what can we talk about what task about which one, if and where they gave a Russian mat, then they gave it near Kyiv and all the ki is worth leaving the Kyiv region Seliger drying, that is, here a bandit, he attacks because he is a bandit and where are you, how then are the cities that are really indicated, they control cinnamon and they do everything there, for example, well, for example, which city is on the throne on the territory of the Russian Federation of personal what cities are located on the territory of the Russian Federation you never know where they recognized Kherson, in my opinion, no, but Kyiv was occupied by no one to write so look, but how much and how much propa in Kherson  la Ukrainian
а сколько в херсоне пропала украинских
people and in Melitopol, that is,
людей и в мелитополе то есть
you just look around, you just don’t see
вы просто осмотрите вы просто не видите
it like that, but we saw I know several
это так а мы видели знаю несколько
reports of people you sell there who were
отчетов людей вы продают там кто был
somehow there about Ukrainian positions, they are
какими то там про украинским позициям их
in ruins when in Russian they are like for a
в руину когда по-русски типа их как на
day
день
in the role of you  they steal people with their blades and
в роли ты их им клинками ворует людей и
they all disappear, that is, there is
все они пропадают то есть идет геноцид
such a genocide, it’s
такой это
not true, I’m lying about that principle, color,
неправда я про тот принципе врут цвет а
but you know a lot about the storm, but
вот куча вы знаете про бучу да
be with the Russians and and
будь у русских да и и
and and and and occupied their Russian troops in the very first days of
и и и и заняли в первые же дни их
such up to  they were knocked out
русские войска таких до их выбили
how many there were tortured Ukrainians before the corpses,
сколько там до трупов было замученных
and
украинцев а
you say you still have to hand over
вы говорите вам надо сдать
no how not
до сих пор нет как нет
look from the first days even aero
смотрите еще с первых дней даже и aero
shots were like that and yes where what corpse
снимки были так и да где какой труп
lay and
лежал а и
exhumations are being carried out now but if people
эксгумации проводят сейчас но если люди
people died during  occupation from the
люди погибли во время оккупации из
back of the head shots, so I’ll tell you about
выстрелов затылок вот я тебя про
Germany, Germany, they don’t believe
германию скажу германии не верят в то
that if it’s
что будь это
Germans, look Germans, they’re talking about Russians,
немцы смотрите немцы они про русские да
yes, you’re completely pro-Russian position, so
вот вас полностью прорусская позиция так
then you support you know
тогда вы поддерживаете знаете
this fascist regime se  now in russia and
этот фашистский режим сейчас в россии и
its economic policy
своей экономической политике
I don’t say how germany germany germany will
не говорю как германия германия германия
support and block the supply of weapons to
поддержит и блокирует поставки оружия
ukraine, and so on until it turns out, but
украине и так дальше до получается а
marx and the legs of the budget Wednesday will already
маркс и ногах среду бюджета будут уж
say dance about the russian position is
говорится танца про российская позиция
very stupid, but in germany they believe that butch
очень глупо но в германии верят что буча
is not a russian fired operation  and whose
это не российская пальнул операция а чья
it is
это
not a racist, I will
не расист я
read the Russian Russian
прочитаю российский российские
German tabloids, which are not but
германские таблоида которые не но то
a bunch of fabricated, that is, it
чтобы куча сфабриковано то есть
turns out that all the corpses who killed the
получается эти все трупы кто убил
Ukrainians and not
украинцы а не
follow this from you are not an investigator, but
следовать этому от вы не следователь но
somewhere on the site they wrote that it was
где то там на сайте написали что это
fabricated, therefore he wrote
сфабрикованное то следовательно писал
that the septic tank
что септика
the newspaper of this garden the
газета этого сада
newspaper which is the German
газета который который немецкая
official position it is
официальная позиция она
sponsored by the state this is the official
государством спонсируется это официально
position of the state bialik wrote that the
позиция государства бялик написал что
bucha they don’t know who initiated there
буча они не знают кто там инициировала
as a bucha but they are not ready to support
как буча но они не готовы поддержать то
what it was but look you admit
что это было а вот смотрите вы признаете
that after all they eat a lot of German politicians
что все таки много немецких политиков
pro-Russian and connected
они съесть пророссийские и связаны
corruptly with  Russian business,
коррупционно с российским бизнесом вот
for example, the same shredder
например тот же шредер
that became, yes, he was in Germany, so
который стал да он был в германии так
top officials, and now, in the growth of oil in
топ чиновников а теперь в рост нефти в
Gazprom, so with the board of directors, the
газпроме так с совете директоров
juice accepted the German mentality, it
сок принимал немецкий менталитет он
will never harm itself if,
никогда не будет себе вредить если
let’s say, in German and
допустим по немецкому и
the German state has a
у немецкого государства есть
need for Russian  gas then she will not
необходимость в русском газе то она не
ever imagine this far away but she
когда-нибудь себе вдаль на эту но она
will turn a blind eye to sacrificing the
будет закрывать глаза на жертвуем
population of ukraine so but work from
населением украине так но работать с
russia to
россии до
such people are very good all thank you
такие люди очень хорошо все спасибо вам
for talking all
за разговор все